Mohammad Salim Baktash

Phone

+93 706 833 150

Email

sstechnologyindtec@gmail.com

Professional Summary

A seasoned programmer with 4 years of experience in different development technologies. I have a passion for solving complex problems and building innovative solutions. My journey in the world of coding has led me to explore various programming languages, tools, databases and technologies.

Mastered Technologies and Topics

Programming Languages Web Development

Python HTML & CSS SQLite3 Bootstrap & TailwindCSS **JavaScript** MySQL Java React.js & Next.js PostgreSQL C/C++ MaterialUi & MantineUl Oracle Dart Flask, Django & FastAPI MongoDB PHP Express.js & Nest.js Redis

Rust SpringBoot

Go TypeORM and GraphQL

Desktop AppMobile AppCloud TechnologiesLinuxQt &PyQtReact NativeGoogle Cloud PlatformLPIC-1AWT & SwingFlutterDockerLPIC-2

Work Experience

2021-2023 | Top in Town Technology

Software Development Instructor

1/1/2024-1/6/2024 | Listoli LLC

Full Stack Developer (Remote)

2023-2024 | Ministry of Culture and Information

Database Management Systems

Full Stack Developer

1/6/2024-until now | Top in Town Technology

Software Development Instructor

Social Media

Linkedin GitHub

linkedin.com/in/mohammad-salim-8453a729b/ github.com/SSTechInd-Tec

Telegram WhatsApp Phone Email

t.me/StarkBak +93 787 311 374 +93 706 833 150 sstechnologyindtec@gmail.com

Education

2011-2022 | Azad Khan High School

High School Degree